(Howard:)Because no one from the future
(Howard:)has come back to kill us.
(Leonard:)Very funny.
(Howard:)You got something better?
(Leonard:)Well, not really.
(Howard:)Okay, then.
(toilet flushes)
(Howard:)Geez, how much wine
did you drink?
(Leonard:)Not a lot. I just couldn't
start until you walked away.
(Sheldon:)The Hell Prawn lunges
out of the hot spring!
(die clinks)
(Sheldon:)You block it with your shield.
(Sheldon:)Do you attack?
(Bernadette:)Does it have eyes?
(Sheldon:)Three giant red ones
and they never blink.
(Sheldon:)It's unsettling.
I stab it in the middle eye!
(die clinks)
Good choice!
Critical hit!
Your sword goes
(Sheldon:)through its eye
into its tiny brain.
(Sheldon:)With its final dying gasp,
it says,
(high-pitched voice):
“You have reduced me
“to a pile of sushi.
“Enjoy me
“with this packet of soy sauce.
It's low sodium.” (groans)